Nothing is more powerful than the human spirit.
The Impossible is a drama, thriller, history film directed by J.A. Bayona.
In December 2004, close-knit family Maria, Henry and their three
sons begin their winter vacation in Thailand.
But the day after Christmas, the idyllic holiday turns into an incomprehensible nightmare when a terrifying roar
rises from the depths of the sea, followed by a wall of black water that devours everything in its path.
Though Maria and her family face their darkest hour, unexpected
displays of kindness and courage ameliorate their terror.
Maria Bennett, played by Naomi Watts.
Henry Bennett, played by Ewan McGregor.
Lucas Bennett, played by Tom Holland.
Thomas Bennett, played by Samuel Joslin.
Simon Bennett, played by Oaklee Pendergast.
Simone, played by Marta Etura.
The Impossible (Spanish: Lo imposible) is a 2012 English-language
Spanish biographical disaster drama film directed by J.
Bayona and written by Sergio G.
It is based on the experience of María Belón and her
family in the 2004 Indian Ocean tsunami.
The Impossible features an international cast, including  Naomi Watts, Ewan
McGregor, and Tom Holland in his live-action film debut.
The film received positive reviews from critics
for its direction and its acting.
For her work in the film, Watts was nominated for the Academy Award for Best Actress, the Golden Globe Award for Best Actress –
Motion Picture Drama, and the Screen Actors Guild Award for Outstanding Performance by a Female Actor in a Leading Role.
The film explores themes of human vs nature, natural
disaster, thailand, based on true story, tsunami.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.